ibay.com.mv 2018-11-17

# Buy & Sell on Maldives No.1 Trade Website | iBay | Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement**  

We respect your privacy. All the information collected on this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned. Any information you give us will be held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. If you have any questions, please [ Contact Us](http://support.ibay.com.mv/index.php?a=add). This Privacy Statement is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

All sensitive transactions on this website are protected by upto 2048-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption in order to ensure that all information exchanged between you and our server are secure.

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
When you visit our web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our web site.

**Personal Information You Choose to Provide**  
_**Registration Information**  
_You will provide us information about yourself when you register to be a member of this site

_**Email & IP Information**.  
_If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. When you register, submit a listing or renew a listing, your IP address is recorded.

_**Web Site Use Information  
**_ Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed and time spent at our Web site. 

**Credit/Debit Card Information  
** We do not collect or store any information regarding your credit/debit card. All card transactions are processed on the respective banks' payment processing site.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide Us?  
**Generally, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by [ Contacting Us](http://support.ibay.com.mv/index.php?a=add)

**What Are Cookies?  
**A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site's computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?  
**As you shop on our Web site, the site uses its cookies to differentiate you from other shoppers so your shopping cart is only available to you. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from seeing unnecessary advertisements or requiring you to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our Web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Web site and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not generally store any personal information that you provided to us in your cookies.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**  
Your information will only be shared to the extent it's necessary to provide the service you requested for. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.Where fraudulent use is reported relating to a listing on this website, we will provide necessary information we have to the investigating authorities. 

**Notice of New Services and Changes**  
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable.
